<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>App Store on S/1999 U 2</title>
    <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/blog/app-store/</link>
    <description>Recent content in App Store on S/1999 U 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Stefanus Secundus.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 22:16:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://s1999u2.github.io/blog/app-store/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Magnet is Damaged</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/macos_magnet_is_damaged/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 22:16:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/macos_magnet_is_damaged/</guid>
      <description>Magnet is Damaged Magnet is a nifty little app that allows Mac users to use Windows-style window snapping1.&#xA;But: I installed Magnet from the App Store, and I&amp;rsquo;m running a current Mac and the latest macOS – how can an app get damaged so that the only way to fix it is to reinstall it? I certainly never had any issue like this on an iPhone.&#xA;If Apple knows exactly how to fix it and Apple runs the App Store – why don&amp;rsquo;t they simply reinstall it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s Privileges</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 08:21:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_4/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Privileges Since iOS and the App Store are Apple&amp;rsquo;s own platforms it gets special privileges and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to follow its own rules. Ever seen any third-party app getting such a nice screen asking for permissions?&#xA;And how about the dark pattern highlighting the Enable Notifications…&#xA;Also: Not Now? How about never?&#xA;Apple gets special treatment when asking for permissions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Dark Patterns</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_3/</guid>
      <description>Services are Apples Next Big Business No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want notifications the first time you asked. Or the second time. So no, I still don&amp;rsquo;t want any notifications, even if you put them inline with the content.&#xA;Apple sneakily trying to spam me. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Ads for Installed Apps</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 14:37:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_2/</guid>
      <description>Apple Knows How to Make the App Store a Premium Experience First, Apple is explicitly showing me something I&amp;rsquo;m not looking for.&#xA;Second, Apple knows Audible is already installed and decides to show me the ad anyway.&#xA;Apple Knows How to Make the App Store a Premium Experience. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Ads for the Top Result</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:30:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/app_store_ads_1/</guid>
      <description>Ads Are Ruining the App Store Hey, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be cool if Apple didn&amp;rsquo;t show the app I&amp;rsquo;m searching for both as a giant ad and as a search result?1&#xA;Ads are ruining Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store. I understand that Crunchy Bagel, the app developer, is not to blame. I genuinely adore Streaks and all of the other apps they offer. You should definitely check them out.&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenVPN Dark Pattern</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/open_vpn_rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:57:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/annoyances/open_vpn_rating/</guid>
      <description>OpenVPN Dark Pattern Okay, so giving the OpenVPN app five stars takes me straight to the App Store. But for anything less, they want me to &amp;ldquo;take a survey&amp;rdquo; 🥵.&#xA;Sure, rate the app. No way, Jose, take a survey. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
