<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on S/1999 U 2</title>
    <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on S/1999 U 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Stefanus Secundus.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 19:58:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s1999u2.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books I Read in 2022</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/books-i-read-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 19:58:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/books-i-read-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got into reading more books again in 2022. The internet and YouTube, in particular, have such a strong pull that I almost have to force myself to take time and dedicate myself to reading something longer than an article. Also, I&amp;rsquo;m a terribly slow reader, which is just unbearable when I see people casually reading twice as fast as me. Still, I found great satisfaction in committing and extending my attention span beyond the instant rewards of today&amp;rsquo;s internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I Learned in 2022</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 19:58:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;Things I Learned in 2022&amp;rdquo;! In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing a list of things that stood out to me as I read and listened to various sources throughout the year. These are things that I found noteworthy and thought-provoking, and I&amp;rsquo;ve included sources for each item as well as summaries of the linked articles or topics for those who are interested in more than just the headline. If you happen to notice any errors, you can reach me on Mastodon at @Secundus@home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I Learned in 2021</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 19:58:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to &amp;ldquo;Things I Learned in 2021&amp;rdquo;! For the second year now, here are noteworthy things that stood out to me during last year.
Hippocampal replay is a phenomenon observed in animals where sequences of cell activations in the hippocampus, a brain region associated with memory and spatial navigation, re-occur during sleep or awake rest at a much faster time scale 🧠🐈🐀⏰. Hippocampal replay is a phenomenon observed in animals where sequences of cell activations in the hippocampus, a brain region associated with memory and spatial navigation, re-occur during sleep at a much faster time scale than during the original activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I Learned in 2020</title>
      <link>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 19:58:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s1999u2.github.io/things-i-learned-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share some of the interesting and unexpected things I came across on the internet in 2020. Without further ado, here are the 25 things that stood out to me.
Brown is not a color, and there is no brown light 🟤🙅‍♂️🎨.
The temperature and atmospheric pressure on Earth can vary greatly across its surface. However, there are lines around the Earth called Isothermal lines and Isobar lines where the temperature and pressure are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
